This summer it's all about sticking together.
American Pie 2 is a comedy, romance film directed by J.B. Rogers.
After a year apart - attending different schools, meeting different people - the
guys rent a beach house and vow to make this the best summer ever.
As it turns out, whether that will happen or not has a lot to do with the girls.
Between the wild parties, outrageous revelations and yes, a trip to band camp, they discover that
times change and people change, but in the end, it's all about sticking together.
Jim Levenstein, played by Jason Biggs.
Kevin Myers, played by Thomas Ian Nicholas.
Chris 'Oz' Ostreicher, played by Chris Klein.
Steve Stifler, played by Seann William Scott.
Paul Finch, played by Eddie Kaye Thomas.
Michelle Flaherty, played by Alyson Hannigan.
American Pie 2 is a 2001 American sex comedy film directed by James B.
Rogers and written by Adam Herz and David H.
Steinberg from a story by Herz.
A sequel to the 1999 comedy film American Pie, it is the second film in the American Pie series and stars Jason Biggs, Shannon Elizabeth, Alyson
Hannigan, Chris Klein, Natasha Lyonne, Thomas Ian Nicholas, Tara Reid, Seann William Scott, Mena Suvari, Eddie Kaye Thomas, and Eugene Levy.
The film follows the sexual exploits of five friends – Jim, Kevin, Stifler, Oz, and Finch – and
their attempts to have the greatest summer party ever at a summer beach house.
American Pie 2 was released in the United States on August 10, 2001 by Universal Pictures, and grossed over $145 million in the United States and
$142 million overseas on a budget of $30 million, making it the highest-grossing film in the franchise at $287.5 million worldwide.
The film was followed by American Wedding (2003).
The film explores themes of summer, beach house,
group of friends, tantra, superglue.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.